careerintelligence.com 2017-11-01

# Career Intelligence - Terms and Conditions

PRIVACY POLICY

At certain points whilst utilising CareerIntelligence.com, information is collected that helps us with the services we provide to our users. 

Guarding your privacy is CareerIntelligence.com's priority and we provide the following statement to inform and assure you of how we look after your information. 

**INFORMATION COLLECTION**

**Registration**  
In order to use some services on CareerIntelligence.com you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password.

During registration you are required to give us your contact information and some demographics. Please enter the information as honestly and accurately as possible so we can tailor the site to our users' needs. 

**Your Friends' E-mail Address**  
Whilst using CareerIntelligence.com, at various points, we offer you the opportunity to send a friend an email telling them about a particular position. We will only use your friend's email address once in order to send this message. After this, they will not be sent any more emails from us unless they voluntarily register to any of our services. 

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user's computer. This is common web technology used by most websites and we use cookies in line with usual and accepted practice.

We use a session cookie to make it easier for you to navigate our site and it expires when you close your browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your internet browser's “help” file. 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by CareerIntelligence.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers or third parties. 

**Web Beacons, Clear GIFS, and Web Bugs**  
CareerIntelligence.com and the advertisers on our site employ a common web tool called Clear GIFS or ‘Web Beacons' on the site and in emails. 

These are used in combination with cookies to allow us to better understand our users' behaviour. They provide us with basic information such as; whether an email has been opened, what has been viewed on the website, which jobs were accessed, etc. 

By using the data provided by these beacons, we are able to evaluate our site and improve our services. Your personal details are in no way linked to the information gathered from the Web Beacons. 

**INFORMATION SHARING AND DISCLOSURE**

We **DO NOT** share your personal information with any third parties. We do share general data that you have provided us such as age, gender, and location to provide broad statistics to third party advertisers and partners. This information does not identify individual users and is not linked to your personally identifiable information. 

We reserve the right to supply personal information in order to comply with the law and to enforce user agreement terms or protect the rights, safety or property of CareerIntelligence.com and its users or others. 

**Choice & 'opt out'**  
When we ask you for your personally identifiable information, we also give you the choice of whether or not you wish to subscribe to our newsletters or third party offers. If, afterwards, you no longer wish to receive these, you may opt out by following the instructions contained within these communications or by logging onto CareerIntelligence.com and editing your profile. 

You will be informed if your personal details will be shared with a third party. You can then make the choice at that point whether to share your details with them.

**Account information, your profile and Curriculum Vitae / resume.**  
When signing up for an account you create a user profile, we then give you the option of attaching your CV/resume and/or video cover letter to your profile and placing it in our CV/resume and/or video cover letter database. 

When you create a profile you have various options to set how much you wish to be accessible to potential employers or recruiters.

Your Profile is always viewable to potential employers and recruiters but you do have the choice to make your personal details confidential, where all of your contact information, salary and even your current place of employment can remain hidden.

When you opt to make sections of your profile private they will stop being accessed by potential employers or recruiters. 

By not allowing parts of your profile to be viewable but still having the information in your profile means that (although we can still use the information to match you to potential jobs and give you a better user experience) employers and recruiters will not have access to it through our profile search database. 

You can store your CV/resume in our database and attach it to your profile, but not allow it to be viewed by potential employers or recruiters without your permission. Not allowing your CV/resume to be viewable means that you can use it to apply for a job online, but employers and recruiters will not have access to it through our CV/resume database.

Employers can search for your CV/resume but they will not be shown any personal information about you. Potential employers or recruiters will then have to forward a request to view any information contained within your CV/resume. Until you give this permission they will not be shown your CV/resume. 

You can allow your CV/resume to be searchable by employers, recruiters, hiring managers, headhunters, and human resource professionals who pay for access to our CV/resume database and your CV/resume. When you opt to make your CV/resume searchable, you still have the choice to make your personal details confidential where all of your contact information and even your current place of employment can remain hidden. 

You can also upload and attach a video cover letter to a CV. The video cover letter will adopt the privacy properties of the CV it is attached to. If a potential employer or recruiter searches for a CV with a video cover letter attached that has been set to private by you, then they will have to send you a request that will have to be approved by you before they can view your CV and video cover letter.

When a potential employer or recruiter views your profile from a CV with a video cover letter the video cover letter will automatically appear in your profile. You can also upload the video cover letter directly to your profile, if you do so this will automatically be viewable to all potential employers or recruiters. 

We use our best efforts to restrict access to our database only to those who have paid for access; these parties may retain a copy of your profile and/or CV/Resume in their own files or databases. We will take reasonable steps to ensure that parties other than those mentioned above will not, without our consent, gain access to this database. 

CareerIntelligence.com is not responsible for the retention, use, or privacy of your profile and/or CV/resume by any third parties. 

You agree that we may share your information with our affiliated companies.

You may remove your Profile and CV/resume from our searchable database at any time by logging into your account or contacting us at: support@CareerIntelligence.com. 

**Updating account and profile information**  
We wish to ensure your personal information is complete, accurate and up to date. 

CareerIntelligence.com allows you to change or correct your details at any time. 

To do so, simply log into your CareerIntelligence.com account and you will find options for editing the information you have submitted. 

**COMMUNICATIONS FROM CareerIntelligence.com**

**Newsletters**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletters, we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. 

We promise to send you no more than two newsletters in a month. With respect for your privacy, we provide you with a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section. 

**Third party offers**  
If you wish to subscribe to our third party offers, we will use your name and email address to send these promotions to you. We promise to send you no more than two of these third party offers in a month. 

With respect for your privacy, we provide you with a way to unsubscribe. Please see the “Choice and Opt-out” section.

**Alerts**  
If you wish to subscribe to one or more of our alerts services, we will use your name and email address to send the job alerts you have requested. You can switch these alerts on and off at your convenience. To check and change the status of your alerts you need to log into your profile. 

**Service-related announcements**  
We will occasionally send you service related announcements when it is necessary, for example, email verification, password resetting or important security and maintenance updates.

Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to delete your account. You must contact our customer service and ask them to this.

**Customer service communication**  
Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcome email to verify your username and password. We will also communicate with you, in response to your enquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email, or in accordance with your wishes. 

**The Security of your Information**  
The security of your personal information is of highest importance to us. When you enter sensitive information such as a credit card number, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). 

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, whilst we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

**Business transitions**  
In the event of CareerIntelligence.com going through a business change, e.g. a merger, acquisition by another company or a sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will most probably be among the assets transferred. 

Users will be notified by email of any change or control of personal information. 

**Changes to this statement**  
We reserve the right to change our Privacy Statement at any time however a notice will be posted on the Website or you will be contacted by email if any important modifications are made. 

Questions or Concerns?   
For any questions or suggestions with regards to our Privacy Statement, please e-mail us and we will be happy to respond.
